[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these items was not invented by Thomas Edison?", "correct_answer": "TV", "incorrect_answers": ["Dictating machine", "3-wire electrical system", "The electric pen"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How long in years is the life span of an average wild hippopotamus?", "correct_answer": "40-50", "incorrect_answers": ["10-20", "30-40", "20-30"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This comedienne, writer and actress, nicknamed Big S, is famous for performing her act as a caricature of a Jewish-American princess.", "correct_answer": "Sarah Silverman", "incorrect_answers": ["Sarah Jessica Parker", "Sarah Michelle Gellar", "Sarah Paulson"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Statue of Liberty was a gift from Italy.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following disease does Propecia (finasteride) treat?", "correct_answer": "Hair loss", "incorrect_answers": ["Nicotine addiction", "Lead poisoning", "Emphysema"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Name the Gus Van Sant movie in which Robert Crawford, a haughty literature professor, accuses Jamal Wallace of plagiarism.", "correct_answer": "Finding Forrester", "incorrect_answers": ["Good Will Hunting", "Beautiful Mind", "Dead Poets Society"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these did the old woman NOT call Princess Buttercup in the film The Princess Bride?", "correct_answer": "Garbage", "incorrect_answers": ["Queen of Putrescence", "Filth", "Queen of Refuse"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these names is used as an alternative name of hazelnuts?", "correct_answer": "Cobnut", "incorrect_answers": ["Cherry nut", "Brown pea", "All of these"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In 1955 pianist Roger Williams had an instrumental hit with this record.", "correct_answer": "Autumn Leaves", "incorrect_answers": ["Summertime", "The Summer Wind", "Why Do I Have Spring Fever"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these names refers to the Asian black bear, a close relative of the American black bear?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Himalayan black bear", "Tibetan black bear", "Moon bear"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of Angelina Jolies first-born biological child?", "correct_answer": "Shiloh", "incorrect_answers": ["Maddox", "Zahara", "Vivienne"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Also called Sea Biscuit, this animal lives in deeper water half-buried in the sand.", "correct_answer": "Sand Dollar", "incorrect_answers": ["Star Fish", "Scallop", "Mussel"]}]